1, Wole Bamiduro Street,
Ahamadiya, Ojokoro, Abule
Egba, Lagos
+2348074508921
dammyadeniye@gmail.com,

ADENIYE DAMILOLA DAVID

Nationality: Nigeria

Religion: Christianity

Date of Birth: 28th December, 1993

State of Origin: Ogun State

Sex: Male

Marital Status: Single

OBJECTIVE:

I strongly believe in hard work. I am a team player and I crave to provide the best services, bringing the best result and qualitative responses, passionate about achieving a challenging professional responsibility that allows meaningful contributions to the development of organization by providing support of all IT Needs that offers growth opportunities and allows me to utilize my leadership skills and experience.

SKILLS & ABILITIES:

- Proficient with MS-office.
- Internet use for research.
- Ability to establish a good working relationship with other professionals.
- Ability to apply technical knowledge related to computer hardware or software.
- Ability to contribute in improving team's performance, skills and technique.
- Able to create a user friendly and dynamic Websites.
- Able to draft plans and follow through on execution.
- Able to manage and manipulate Database system.
- Able to balance customer service with technology constraint.

Areas of Expertise

- Website Development
- Database Management
- Project Management Help Desk support
- Microsoft office Packages
 Customer Service
- Application support

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Industrial Training. United Global Resource Limited (UGRL)

April – September 2014.

- Troubleshooting and System Maintenance.
- Designing and Developing of web platforms
- Able to create a user friendly and dynamic Websites.
- Able to manage and manipulate Database system.
- Operation and Maintenance of the ICT Unit Infrastructure.
- Interact confidently with staff to analyse and evaluate their demands with Regards to Computer use.
- Creating application software
- Involved in Training and computer literacy programme for staff.

TITIS (TRANTER IT) Lafarge Holcim

February 5, 2017– Till date

- Joined a team of professionals in a rigorous training on help desk support, service desk and all that entails IT service and its infrastructure.
- Provided Application support and contribute technical support while on site.
- Ability to diagnose and resolve basic technical issues
- Ability to use various support tools to manage clients (MANAGE ENGINE, SAP and HODIM)
- Ability to determine the best solution based on the issue and details provided by the user
- Ability to provide accurate information on IT product or services

PEACOCK MALL

October 5, 2017-December, 2017

- Managed social media platform
- Provided the SEO to optimize their platform
- Ability to generate traffic.
- Monitored the activities on the site using google analytic

Assistant Operations Officer. Goldmine Techno-Solar Ltd

April 11,2016 - August 26,2016.

- Joined a team of professionals in installing solar panels and inverter.
- Provided logistics support and contributed technical support while on site.

Assistant Operations Officer. Panayo Ltd

August 30,2016 – November 2016.

- Joined a team of professionals in deploying IP camera, CCTV & PABX System.
- Provided logistics support and contributed technical support while on site.

National Youth Service. Atakumosa Senior High School Osu, Osun State.

November 2015 - November 2016

- Computer Science Tutor.
- Conduct assigned classes at the times scheduled.
- Worked cooperatively with school administrators, students, parents, other Teachers and colleagues.
- Implement designated support to the school computer laboratory and its Maintenance

Education

- Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo.
 B.Sc. Computer Science 2011-2015
- Mayors Height College,

10 Oluwaleyimu street, Ikeja, Lagos SSCE (WASSCE). 2004 - 2010

 Morolu Nursery and Primary School 10 Oluwaleyimu street, Ikeja, Lagos First School Leaving Certificate 1996-2003

Professional Certifications

Computer Professional Registration Council of Nigeria.

Graduate Member

Human Resource Management

Ultra brains institute

Project Management Professional

Classic System InfoTech

ITIL (Information Technology Infrastructure Library)

Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE)

Other Certifications

Website Design and Development Oracle Database 11g (OCA) Core Java

United Global Resource Limited (UGRL). 91 Allen avenue Lagos.

National Youth Service (NYSC)

Atakumosa Senior High School Osu, Osun State.

Closed Circuit Television Certified CCTV

Panayo

Solar and inverter installation

Goldmine Techno-Solar Itd

Database Management System

Exstream.

HOBBIES

Volleyball, Indoor Games Researching, Travelling and Meeting people.

REFERENCES

PROF. J.O. ADENIYI.

The Dean Faculty of Natural Sciences, Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo. Jadeniyi@hotmail.com

MD/CEO of Goldmine Techno-Solar Itd 2, Jogunsinmi street, off Awolowo way, ikeja Lagos Goldminetechnosolar@gmail.com

Mr. Makinde Oladayo Lecturer of Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo State 08032068784